seobuckle.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy | SEO-Buckle

This Privacy Policy explains how data distribution and processing work in SEOBuckle.com which is owned and controlled by Anonima EM Network Inc. We want you to understand how we may use your data, before and after you provide it. The purpose of this policy is to inform you of what type of data (if any) we gather and track, how we may use that data, and with whom we may share that data.

### Your Personal Data :

SEOBuckle.com is a non-membership service, it is available for everyone, from any part of the world, and for free. You can visit SEOBuckle.com on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal data about yourself. However, you may choose to give us personal data in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us data such as your name and address or e-mail ID so we may get in contact with you, or provide you with subscription or service opportunities (if we have any in the future). If you tell us that you do not want us to use data you provide to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you give us personal data about somebody else, we will assume that you have their prior permission to do so and will not take any responsibility for it.

### Using and Sharing Personal Data :

The following paragraphs describe in more detail how we may use the data you provide to us on the SEOBuckle.com site and with whom we may share it. Depending on the part of the SEOBuckle.com site you are visiting, one or more of the following paragraphs may apply -

*  **Fulfilling Your Request :**

If you request something from or through the SEOBuckle.com Web site (for example, more data on a product or service or a callback) we will use the data you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share data with others. For instance, our affiliates, business partners, financial institutions, or postal or government authorities may participate in fulfilling your request.

*  **Marketing Use :**

We will not use data you provide unless you give us your permission to do so.

*  **Links to Other Websites :**

In some cases, when you are seeking further data about a person you are searching, you may see links or advertisements about data and data available to you through other websites. For example, if you find a site through the SEOBuckle.com site, you may be able to gather more detailed data such as a phone number or address, subject to certain terms and conditions. You should carefully review the privacy and personal data policies of any advertised or linked websites before providing any personal data or purchasing any product or service from them. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third party Web sites.

### Data Security :

We protect your personal data and maintain its quality. We implement measures and processes to help us keep your data secure.

*  **Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Web Technologies :**

We sometimes collect non-identifiable data from visits to the SEOBuckle.com site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we measure visitor activity on SEOBuckle.com, but we do so in ways that keep our visitor's identities anonymous. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better user service.

We collect the data we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You also can set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly.

*  **Online Advertising :**

Certain companies help us deliver interactive on-line advertising. These companies may collect and use data about customers to help us better understand the offers, promotions, and types of advertising that are most appealing to our customers. After the data is collected, it is aggregated so it is not identifiable to a specific individual.

*  **Disclosures Required By Law :**

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal data may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.

*  **Enforcement :**

SEOBuckle.com regularly reviews its compliance with this policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this. It is our policy to contact the inquiring user regarding his or her questions.

### Changes to this Policy :

This Privacy Policy may occasionally change. Any Policy changes will be posted to this page. Each version of this policy will be denoted at the top of this page by its effective date.
